

Personal Website: kevin0920.github.io | kevinlingsike@gmail.com

Innovative, energetic and motivated, full stack, front to backend software engineer with extensive training in software development in programming languages, applications and protocols across several platforms eagerly seeks learning challenges with functional-design team to produce outstanding products. Highly reliable and confident professional.

## **SOFTWARE SKILLS**

Languages:HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, JavaBackend:Django, Node.js, Express.js, Flask, MongooseDatabases:MySQL, MongoDB, FireStoreFrameworks:Flask, Django, Node.JS, Angular 4, React.JS

Libraries: JQuery, Bootstrap, Materialize, Font-Awesome Architecture: OOP, REST

Web Tech: HTTP, TCP/IP, AJAX Miscellaneous: Git, AWS, Heroku, Adobe Photoshop

## **PROJECTS**

Place order Website (Team Project): built in MEAN framework which uses MongodB as database, angular4, bootstrap,
Express, Socket.io, Node.JS, Bootstrap, jQuery, HTML, CSS. The first user account will the website admin can create menu in
detail. The future users can either choose google social login or regular login to placing orders, then when the order submitted,
will receive confirmation emails with order detail and total amount of the purchase. For user experience, there is total online
user section and total order history for related account, and people can like the specific food they might purchase again.
 Source code: https://github.com/Kevin0920/food-copy

Deploy link: https://pure-fortress-43994.herokuapp.com/

 Booking Events: MEAN Frame work, login users create different events will separate by different states with CRUD feature, people can join the event and post comments for each one, and can cancel join status. Event create can edit or delete event.
 Source code: <a href="https://github.com/Kevin0920/fullmean-events">https://github.com/Kevin0920/fullmean-events</a>

Deploy link: https://serene-castle-65373.herokuapp.com/

• **Q&A/Market Trade:** MEAN framework, users post questions for others answering, and keep tracking and counting the total number of answers. Also, people can like the answers. Another feature is making posts for selling products with listing the detail of products. Products with image and detail display or render in home page randomly.

Source code: https://github.com/Kevin0920/fullmean-marketplace-QA

Deploy link: https://young-basin-45853.herokuapp.com/

## **EXPERIENCE**

Coding Dojo (Certification), (San Jose, CA), June 2017 – Sep 2017

One of the highest-rated coding boot camps in the world, and teaching three full technology stacks in a single 14-week program. Courses involved immersive web Development boot camp specializing in front-end and Full Stack fundamentals, enabling comprehensive front to backend project management and control.

Graphic Design Assistant, Duxwell Printing, (San Francisco, CA), July 2016 – April 2017

Provided timely, detailed, and personalized custom printing and graphics design, consultation, typography and printing services with Adobe's InDesign and Photoshop. Produced brochures, business cards, booklets, labels and flyers for numerous brands. Effectively managed daily operations; Assigned personnel according to required tasks.

• Assisted in the planning of product offerings; prepared detailed, research based Sales and Stock Plans over Yelp.

Customer Svc/Marketing/Product Support, Shaklee Corp. (Pleasanton, CA), Oct 2015 – July 2016

Extended superb reception and administrative services including call management to address customer needs and achieve customer satisfaction. Accurately rendered complete details of the Shaklee Compensation Plan to include specific bonusqualification rules and volume requirements for all Shaklee distributors.

- · Managed and maintained company's Product Ordering System; tracked all shipments via FedEx or Postal Service.
- · Proficiently completed Chinese/English and English/Chinese translation for the sales and marketing team.
- Utilized Excel for analyzing the daily, weekly, monthly call volume levels.

IT Support (Intern), California Nurses Association (Oakland, CA), Jan 2012 – April 2012

Managed computer hardware system to run services for network users; installed, updated, configured and monitored account bookings and system for company supplies. Processed requests and delivered data to client computers over a local network or the Internet, often configured to handle client service load.

## **EDUCATION**